<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sitemap on GovCloud</title>
    <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sitemap on GovCloud</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:10:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-11-19</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/11-15-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/11-15-18/</guid>
      <description>  Minutes taken by: Zachary Seguin
 Presentation Presentation was given by Sani Chabi Yo senior solution architect at MongoDB and one of the maintainers of the MongoDB Operator.
 MongoDB Operator Atlas Stitch  The complete video has been updated to our youtube channel and the slide deck can be found below.
 MongoDB Slides  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-10-12</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/10-12-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/10-12-18/</guid>
      <description>  Minutes taken by: Zachary Seguin
 Presentation Presentation was given by Liz Rice Co-Chair of many KubeCons and maintainer of various security oriented applications around Kubernetes.
 Kube-Hunter Kube-Bench  The complete video has been updated to our youtube channel and the slide deck can be found below.
 Aqua Slides  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-09-28</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/09-28-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/09-28-18/</guid>
      <description>Presentation Presentation was given for Open First Day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-08-26</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/08-26-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/08-26-18/</guid>
      <description>Minutes taken by: Zachary Seguin
 Post Discussion  More flexibility with some of the timing Procurement people are allowed to come into presentations Full remote meetings would be a big plus  Still have issues with some departments blocking access Face to Face is of course important though and will be main type of meetup  Interest in talking to people who have taken Kubernetes all the way into production Request to ask if we can get Jonathan Pulcifier (Security) at Shopify Interest in hosting a Kubernetes Basics Course Serverless talks on:  Lambda When to use versus containers KNative  GCTools is willing to do a demo Chris Allison wants to help and better support communities that to exist We can apparently get translation and transcription Desire for focused problem sets and interactive demos Mentioned dev.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-06-26</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/06-26-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/06-26-19/</guid>
      <description>  Minutes taken by: Zachary Seguin
 Introduction Brief introduction of new members
Planning Items Meeting ran late so no new planning items so can get right into presentation.
Minutes Meeting ran late so no reading of minutes so can get right into presentation.
Presentation Ross Clarke of Statistics Canada gave a thorough presentation of Terraform.
 Benefits of Terraform for Hybrid Cloud Terraform Demo Terraform integration with Azure  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-05-29</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/05-29-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/05-29-18/</guid>
      <description>Minutes taken by: Zachary Seguin
 Introduction Brief Introduction of new members
Planning Items Starting to hit our stride now and meetings for next 2 months are planned.
As mentioned we are always looking for constructive criticism and are currently enacted the two we have already recieved:
 More focused on specific topics Don&amp;rsquo;t assume users are familiar with fundamentals  We did also get some positive feedback:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-04-24</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/04-24-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/04-24-18/</guid>
      <description>Minutes taken by: Zachary Seguin
 Introduction Canadian Digital Services - Collaboration Room
 Canadian Digital Services / Statistics Canada organized Importance of Cloud native As Developers our view points aren&amp;rsquo;t always appreciated Policy makers make decisions and we enact it  Minutes But first we need to quickly go over some highlight from the minutes during the last meetup.
 Review of planning decisions from last meeting Website govcloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetups</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/</guid>
      <description>Overview We ask that you register for our working group and that you at least provide your real full name when signing up.
 Cloud Native @ GoC Meetup  Meetups are usually held once a month at:
Canadian Digital Service
219 Laurier Ottawa, ON
Room 14003 on the 14th floor
  Notice: This meetup is for Government of Canada employees only. We intend to invite outside partners for special events, i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minutes for 2018-03-22</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/03-22-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/meetup/03-22-18/</guid>
      <description>Minutes taken by: Zachary Seguin
 Introduction Canadian Digital Services - Collaboration Room
 Canadian Digital Services / Statistics Canada organized Importance of Cloud native As Developers our view points aren&amp;rsquo;t always appreciated Policy makers make decisions and we enact it  Vision  Long road, not everything can be done by cloud native IaaS formulas, Amazon, Azure, etc. is not cloud native Should focus on purely cloud native, can go any cloud If it&amp;rsquo;s been solved in cloud native, we should take and learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:10:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://govcloud.github.io/sitemap/slides/</guid>
      <description>Slidedecks for presentations given during the recurring monthly Cloud Native @ Government of Canada meetup:
 03-22-18 04-24-18 05-29-18 06-26-18 08-26-18 09-28-18 10-12-18 11-15-18  Special Presentations:
 Open First Day (2018)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>